thedenveregotist.com 2014-05-29

# Privacy Policy - The Denver Egotist

**Purpose of this privacy policy**  
This privacy policy describes how The Denver Egotist and its parent company, The Egotist, LLC, treats the personal information that we have collected about you when you visit and use our service. Your use of this website constitutes consent to use of your personal information collected by us as outlined herein.

**What data do we collect?**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. This includes but is not limited to registration and profile information, IP addresses, referral pages, site behavior, comments, traffic data and any communication occurring between you and us. We do not track your information or behavior on any third party locations or services unrelated to The Denver Egotist.

**What do we plan to do with this data?**  
Your data serves one main function: By storing and tracking this information, we hope to gain a better understanding of site usage behavior and to subsequently improve the content and offerings on our site.

**Your data and third parties**  
We do not sell or rent any of your personally identifying data to third parties for direct marketing purposes. We do not collect specific member address information, so this is a moot point regardless.

We may share or disclose information about you to other companies or individuals when: (1) We must comply with applicable laws, regulations, or legal or regulatory process; (2) to properly operate the website, and (3) in the event of a sale, merger, transfer, or exchange of control of The Denver Egotist or its assets to another party.

**What information can I access?**  
You can access your personal information on our website and correct, amend or delete information that is inaccurate. Upon logging in, visit your user profile settings page located at: <http://www.thedenveregotist.com/user>. Upon request, we're happy to provide access to any site behavior data that we have collected about you. All requests for such data will be fulfilled within a 14-day period.

**Communications with members**  
When you register with The Denver Egotist, you will be automatically opted-in to receive email and in-system notices, which may include announcements, newsletters and recommendations. 

**Public sharing of your data**  
The Denver Egotist allows the public and other members of the site to browse your public profile. The Denver Egotist allows other users to browse your username, real name, description, city of residence, links to you elsewhere online, your specialties, and uploaded samples of your work. The Denver Egotist also allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the website.

**Removal of user and user data**  
We will not remove posts on a per-post basis save in the exception of copyright protection or dispute, see our Terms & Conditions for more on our copyright policies. If you would like your user profile removed from The Denver Egotist, login to your profile at: <http://www.thedenveregotist.com/user>.

**Data breach**  
In the event of a data breach, we will comply with the applicable law set forth in the Terms and Conditions, with respect to such data breach.

**Terms and conditions**  
The Terms and Conditions governing use of this website are incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to privacy policy**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time in our discretion. Your continued use of the website constitutes your consent to this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time. This policy was last updated on June 17, 2013. 

**Contact informatino**  
If you have any questions or notices of violations to this Privacy Policy, please contact the editor of The Denver Egotist by sending an email to [the@denveregotist.com](mailto:the@denveregotist.com).
